Idina Menzel - Let It Go (From "Frozen")
오늘 밤, 산 위의 눈은 하얗게 빛나고
The snow glows white on the mountain tonight
발자국조차 보이지 않아
Not a footprint to be seen
이 고독한 왕국에서
A kingdom of isolation
난 여왕인 것 같아
And it looks like I'm the queen
마치 폭풍 속에 있는 것처럼 바람은 휘몰아쳐
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside
더는 견딜 수가 없어, 하늘도 내가 노력한 걸 알아
Couldn't keep it in, heaven knows I've tried
그들을 들이지 말고 보이게도 하지 마
Don't let them in, don't let them see
"착한 여자아이가 되어라, 항상 그래야만 해"
Be the good girl you always have to be
감춰버려, 신경쓰지마, 그들이 알지 못하게 해
Conceal, don't feel, don't let them know
뭐 이젠 알았겠지
Well, now they know
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
더 이상 견딜 수가 없어
Can't hold it back anymore
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
돌아서서 문을 쾅 닫아버려
Turn away and slam the door
난 이제 신경쓰지 않아
I don't care
남들이 뭐라고 하던지 말이야
what they're going to say
폭풍이 몰아치도록 내버려 둬
Let the storm rage on
추위는 아무것도 아니었거든
The cold never bothered me anyway
멀어지니 작게 보이네. 참 재밌지
It's funny how some distance
makes everything seem small
한 때 날 뒤덮은 두려움은 이제 아무것도 아냐
And the fears that once controlled me
can't get to me at all
이제 내가 뭘 할 수 있나 봐야지
It's time to see what I can do
한계를 시험하고 뛰어넘을거야
To test the limits and break through
옳고 그름, 규칙은 내게 없어
No right, no wrong, no rules for me
나는 자유로워
I'm free
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
난 하늘, 바람과 함께 할거야
I am one with the wind and sky
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
너흰 내가 우는 모습을 볼 수 없을걸
You'll never see me cry
난 이 곳에 서있어
Here I stand
이 곳이 내가 머물 곳이야
and here I'll stay
폭풍이 몰아치도록 내버려 둬
Let the storm rage on
내 힘이 눈처럼 흩날려 땅에 내려앉고
My power flurries through the air into the ground
내 정신은 눈꽃을 타고 올라
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around
내겐 칼바람처럼 확고한 생각이 있어
And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast
절대 돌아가지 않을거야
I'm never going back
지난 일은 과거 속에 묻어둬
the past is in the past
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
새벽이 밝아오는 것처럼 일어설거야
And I'll rise like the break of dawn
이젠 내버려둬
Let it go, let it go
완벽한 여자아인 이제 없어
That perfect girl is gone
난 이 곳에 서있어
Here I stand
태양 아래 이 곳에
in the light of day
폭풍이 몰아치도록 내버려 둬
Let the storm rage on
추위는 아무것도 아니었거든
The cold never bothered me anyway